(upbeat music)
♪ What I want, you've got and
it might be hard to handle ♪
♪ But like a flame that burns the candle ♪
♪ The candle feeds the flame ♪
♪ Yeah, what I've got ♪
♪ Full stock of thoughts
and dreams that scatter ♪
♪ And you pull them all together,
and how, I can't explain ♪
♪ Oh yeah, well, well, you ♪
♪ You, you, ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ You make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ Well, well, well you ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Oh yeah, you make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ On a night when bad
dreams become a screamer ♪
♪ When they're messing with the dreamer ♪
♪ I can laugh it in the face ♪
♪ Twist and shout my way out
and wrap yourself around me ♪
♪ 'Cause I ain't the way you found me ♪
♪ And I'll never be the same ♪
♪ Oh yeah, well, 'cause you ♪
♪ You, you, ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ You make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ Well, well, well you ♪
♪ Ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ You make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ Well, listen to this ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
(upbeat music)
♪ I'm down on my daydream ♪
♪ Oh, that sleepwalk should
be over by now, I know ♪
♪ Well, you ♪
♪ Yeah, you make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ I've been waiting for,
waiting for you, girl ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Oh yeah, you make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ I've been waiting for,
waiting for you, girl ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ Oh my, you make my dreams come true ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ Whoa ooh whoa, I've been waiting for ♪
♪ Waiting for, waiting for, waiting for ♪
♪ You make my dreams ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh, you ♪
♪ I've been waiting for you, girl ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ooh ooh ♪
♪ You make my dreams ♪
♪ You, you, you, ooh ooh ooh ♪